<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<item>
  <id>HE-PVC</id>
  <date>2006-01-01</date>
  <category>04-01-03</category>
  <position>1</position>
  <icon>
    <deutsch>he-pvc_3fach.small.png</deutsch>
    <english>he-pvc_3fach.small.png</english>
    <français>he-pvc_3fach.small.png</français>
  </icon>
  <image>
    <deutsch>he-pvc_3fach.png</deutsch>
    <english>he-pvc_3fach.png</english>
    <français>he-pvc_3fach.png</français>
  </image>
  <name>
    <deutsch>HE-PVC</deutsch>
    <english>HE-PVC</english>
    <français>HE-PVC</français>
  </name>
  <headline>
    <deutsch>Haengeelektrode -einfach, mehrfach-</deutsch>
    <english>Suspended electrode -simple, multiple-</english>
    <français>Electrode suspendue -simple, multiple-</français>
  </headline>
  <description>
    <deutsch>Geeignet fuer alle leitfaehigen, aggressiven Medien (z.B. Saeuren, Laugen), 
				waessrige Loesungen, Wasser, Abwasser oder andere leitfaehige Fluessigkeiten
				Fuehlerstaebe aus: Edelstahl, Hastelloy B und C, Titan und Tantal
				Haengeausfuehrungen fuer grosse Tiefen oder schwierige Montagebedingungen
				Verstellbare Ausfuehrungen zur nachtraeglichen Anpassung der Schaltpunkte
				Sonderausfuehrungen und spezielle Elektroden nach Kundenwuenschen moeglich</deutsch>
    <english>Appropriate for all conductive, aggressive media (e.g. acids, bases), aqueous solutions, 
				water, sewage or other conductive liquids
				Detector bar made of : special steel, Hastelloy B and C, titanium and tanalium
				Suspended type for large depths or difficult assembly conditions
				Adjustable types for subsequent adjustment of the shifting points
				Special types and special electrodes upon customer requests</english>
    <français>Approprié pour tous les media conductibles, agressifs (p.ex. acides, lessives alcalines), 
				solutions aqueuses, eau, eaux usées ou d´autres liquides conductibles
				Détecteurs en baguette: acier inox, hastelloy B et C, titane et tantale
				Types suspendus pour les profondeurs importantes ou des conditions de montage difficiles
				Type ajustable pour l´adaptation ultérieure des points de commutation
				Construction spéciale et électrodes spéciales sur demande du client</français>
  </description>
  <datasheet>
    <deutsch>
      <name>Datenblatt</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-E-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </deutsch>
    <english>
      <name>Datasheet</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-E-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </english>
    <français>
      <name>Fiche de données</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-F-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </français>
  </datasheet>
</item>
