<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<item>
  <id>ST-1...5fach</id>
  <date>2006-01-01</date>
  <category>04-01-03</category>
  <position>1</position>
  <icon>
    <deutsch>st-1___5fach.small.png</deutsch>
    <english>st-1___5fach.small.png</english>
    <français>st-1___5fach.small.png</français>
  </icon>
  <image>
    <deutsch>st-1___5fach.png</deutsch>
    <english>st-1___5fach.png</english>
    <français>st-1___5fach.png</français>
  </image>
  <name>
    <deutsch>ST 1...5fach</deutsch>
    <english>ST 1...5fach</english>
    <français>ST 1...5fach</français>
  </name>
  <headline>
    <deutsch>Stellelektrode mit von aussen verschiebbaren Staeben</deutsch>
    <english>Adjustable electrode with bars to be slid from the outside</english>
    <français>Electrode d´ajustement avec des baguettes mobiles de l´extérieur</français>
  </headline>
  <description>
    <deutsch>Geeignet fuer alle leitfaehigen, aggressiven Medien (z.B. Saeuren, Laugen), 
				waessrige Loesungen, Wasser, Abwasser oder andere leitfaehige Fluessigkeiten
				Gewindeanschluesse aus: PE, PPH, PVC, PTFE, PVDF und Edelstahl (1.4571)
				Fuehlerstaebe aus: Edelstahl, Hastelloy B und C, Titan und Tantal
				Verstellbare Ausfuehrungen zur nachtraeglichen Anpassung der Schaltpunkte
				Sonderausfuehrungen und spezielle Elektroden nach Kundenwuenschen moeglich</deutsch>
    <english>Appropriate for all conductive, aggressive media (e.g. acids, bases), aqueous solutions, 
				water, sewage or other conductive liquids
				Threaded connections and housings made of : PE, PPH, PVC, PTFE, PVDF and special steel (1.4571)
				Detector bar made of : special steel, Hastelloy B and C, titanium and tanalium
				Adjustable types for subsequent adjustment of the shifting points
				Special types and special electrodes upon customer requests</english>
    <français>Approprié pour tous les media conductibles, agressifs (p.ex. acides, lessives alcalines), 
				solutions aqueuses, eau, eaux usées ou d´autres liquides conductibles
				Raccords filetés et boîtier en: PE, PPH, PVC, PTFE, PVDF et acier inox (1.4571) 
				Détecteurs en baguette: acier inox, hastelloy B et C, titane et tantale 
				Type ajustable pour l´adaptation ultérieure des points de commutation
				Construction spéciale et électrodes spéciales sur demande du client</français>
  </description>
  <datasheet>
    <deutsch>
      <name>Datenblatt</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-E-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </deutsch>
    <english>
      <name>Datasheet</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-E-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </english>
    <français>
      <name>Fiche de données</name>
      <path>04/04-01-03-F-stell_haenge-elektroden.pdf</path>
    </français>
  </datasheet>
</item>
